


<resources>

    <string name = "name_blando" >Alejandro Blando</string>
    <string name = "name_lloyd" >Christian Lloyd Salon</string>
    <string name = "name_calape" >Philip John Calape</string>
    <string name = "name_lipa" > Neil Ryan Lipa-od</string>
    <string name = "name_kin" >Christian Kin Lascuña</string>


    <string name = "track_blando" >Android</string>
    <string name = "track_lloyd" >Android</string>
    <string name = "track_calape" >Father Rasta</string>
    <string name = "track_lipa" >Junior dev for life</string>
    <string name = "track_kin" >iOS</string>


    <string name = "description_blando" >Replica of the great Rastaman himself. The Android dev and supreme leader of the team, with skills much like Rastaman himself as he leads the Philippines as president</string>

    <string name = "description_lloyd" >Codename Half-Human Half-Zombie of Android. Just like Rastaman, he has the skills of both halves: the great coding skills of a human and the nonstop coding capability of a zombie. Anong branch branch, sa main agad</string>

    <string name = "description_calape" >Direct shadow apostle of Nil Pogi, the backend lord. He acquires a great buff in coding in java spring in the presence of his master, much as he is enlightened by Rastaman himself.</string>

    <string name = "description_lipa" >The backend lord, the java god, the spring guru. Not only is his skills already in senior dev level even if he is still a trainee, he is also really pogi, more pogi than the great Rastaman.</string>
    <string name = "description_kin" >"The one man team IOS developer in Rasta Tech. He can get things done with great perfection even if alone due to the blessing of Rastamans's Dark Angel"</string>

    <string name = "quotes_blando" >Push Na yan sa Main, Warning lang naman</string>
    <string name = "quotes_lloyd" >Anong branch branch, sa main agad</string>
    <string name = "quotes_calape" >While theres a code, there are bugs, Kaya madami akong Baygon sa bahay</string>
    <string name = "quotes_lipa" >Anong review review?</string>
    <string name = "quotes_kin" >Theres no I in team, only in Kin</string>

</resources>